(Howard:)...the only wand that ever saw any action
was this one.
Oh! Look what my mom
made us for the act.
(Howard:)Well, she cut up
one of her old bathing suits.
(Howard:)She made these two vests
and haIf a dozen napkins.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Has she tried on the vest yet?
l just gave it to her.
- I hope it fits.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)She has a tricky figure.
She's short and stacked like me.
(Howard:)She's not stacked like you, Ma.
She never steps on hers.
(Bernadette:)Listen, Howie. Maybe I'm not the
best choice to be a magician's assistant.
(Howard:)You'll do fine. Hand me those rings?
(Howard:)See? You nailed it.
No, it's just that I'm not
that comfortable with little kids.